A Guide to the Papers of Michael D'Orso
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Series V: Audio, Video, Computer disks
  - 3 1/2" disk - "Disk one - contents, title, part one-five" (Box Box 15)
  - 3 1/2 " disk - "Disk two - part six: thanks, book notes, characters" (Box Box 15)
  - 3 1/2" disk - "Rosewood - prologue & ch. 1-12 (Box Box 15)
  - 3 1/2 " disk - "Rosewood - 47 file/all chapters" (Box Box 15)
  - 3 unlabeled 3 1/2" disks (Box Box 15)